

Pratik Vermun

Learning for life

CONTACT DETAILS



pvermun@gmail.com



+91-7838162644



Id:Pratik vermuns



Linkedin.com/Pratik-vermun



New Delhi,India

MANAGERIAL SKILLS

- Sales Planning and Forecasting
- Identifying, recruiting and motivating sales reps
- Team Management-Daily morning meet with the team. Set agenda for the day and discussion on previous day's work
- Problem solving
- Analytical Thinking
- **Building Relationships**
- Positive outlook

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- ReactJS
- NextJS
- NodeJS/Express
- Vanilla JavaScript
- Bootstrap/Sass
- **GIT**



About me

Meticulous and motivated web developer with a flair for creating elegant solutions in the least amount of time. Developed an E-chat webapp, a Netflix-clone app, and a GitHub profile card using React as a front-end tool and firebase for managing back-end.

Passionate about responsive and elegant web design with a firm believer of mobile first approach.



Projects

New website for Globepaddler (a Swiss Kayaking company) (Ongoing)

Currently working on a project which requires a complete overhaul of the UI and an admin dashboard. Using Next.JS as a frontend SSR tool and Strapi(headless CMS) for content management.

Job Dashboard for Global Talent Accelerator(GTA), Canada (Ongoing)

> Developing a jobs search and result dashboard using React.

Portfolio Website

- Showcases my React and vanilla JavaScript skills. A repository for my various React/JavaScript/Sass/Bootstrap projects done over a period of past 1 year. Also contains some DOM games. All of my projects are hosted on Firebase.
- https://pratikdev.net/



Work Experience ———

Associate Unit Head, Sales- Pramerica Life Insurance Ltd. June,2019-June,2020

- Presented a prototype of a mobile app, where our policy holders could see their policy details and the loyal and premium paying customers would get loyalty points. Customers would accumulate more loyalty points through referrals and policy consistency, which would then be redeemed via various e-commerce platforms.
- Was responsible for every aspect of sales from team hiring training till closure.

Freelance Web Developer (2015-2017)



Education

2017-2019

MBA in Marketing and HR IIM Rohtak, India

2010-2015

Masters in Geophysical Technology IIT Roorkee, India

2009

CBSE Board Delhi, India